

RDUBPhoto@gmail.com 773.789.7152

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Obtain a challenging leadership position applying creative problem solving and lean management skills with a growing company.

PROFILE

Professional Web/Graphic Design - Extensive experience in UI/UX, web & print production. Developed corporate branding identities, global web sites, advertisements, brochures, flyers, banners and storefront signs for clients both in retail and corporate services.

Creative Team Player - Known for creativity, flexibility, and a great sense of humor. Former co-employee noted: "Robert is one of the quickest and most thorough coworkers I've worked with. He has an open mind when it comes to designing the best for the client's needs."

SOFTWARE & TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite (CS6)QuarkAutoCADMicrosoft OfficeApertureFlashHTML 5 & CSSWindowsMac OSXEmailVisioPrint Production

LESS CSS JavaScript Visual Studio Responsive Web Design

EDUCATION

The Illinois Institute of Art - Chicago

Chicago, IL

Major: Visual Communication / Graphic Design

GPA: 3.4 / 4.0

Courses: Image Manipulation, Digital Photography, Design Fundamentals, Observational Drawing, Typography, and Rapid

Visualization.

Cincinnati State Cincinnati, OH Major: Architecture GPA: 3.2 / 4.0

Courses: AutoCAD, Hand Drafting, Surveying, and

Construction Fundamentals.

CAREER RELATED EXPERIENCE

MaintenanceNet

Carlsbad, CA

UI / UX Designer & Front End Developer

April 2012 - April 2013

- Learning and applying the latest technologies for the ServiceExchange application. (LessCSS, HTML5, CSS3, KendoUI)
- Cleanup of existing CSS/HTML for V1 and other in-place applications to ensure proper up-to-datecode with cross browser compatibility.
- UI / UX support for all project management teams to ensure the application design and functionality is cutting-edge for the end-client
- PPT templates & Presentation support for all sales and marketing teams
- Support production and auto-quote teams with imagery and html coding for cross-email compatibility

Clover Technologies

Hoffman Estates, IL

Sr. Global Web Designer

June 2010 - January 2012

- Managing and designing multiple global websites
- · Developing new concept designs for new branding strategies
- · Coordinating new product announcements and newsletter eBlasts on a weekly basis
- Created new and innovative package design for retail sales

Doculabs

Chicago, IL

Graphic Designer

September 2007 - April 2010

- Specialized in the creation of proposals and deliverables for top corporation IT consulting
- · Printing, binding, and organization of materials for delivery of consulting collateral
- Collaborating and designing of past and present projects for slideshow marketing presentations